toxel.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Toxel.com

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used, and **Toxel.com** will make every effort to ensure that its activities keep within the spirit of this Privacy Policy.

Please note that by visiting and using **Toxel.com** , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## Requested Information

**Toxel.com** may request your name, e-mail address, website address or any other necessary information for the purposes of conducting a survey, adding you to the mailing list, or by your request to have someone contact you for additional information. Whenever **Toxel.com** requests the identity of a visitor, **Toxel.com** will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. **Toxel.com** maintains a strict “ **No Spam** ” policy that means **Toxel.com** does not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent.

In addition, **Toxel.com** will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you are a member of the Mailing List, you will be contacted with announcements, news, and new products or services. You have the option of “Unsubscribing” from the Mailing List at any time, thereby disabling any further such e-mail communication from being sent to you.

## Disclosure

**Toxel.com** will disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to:

– Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on **Toxel.com**.

– Protect and defend the rights or property of **Toxel.com** , or visitors of **Toxel.com**.

– Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties.

– Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

**Toxel.com** uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to it secure. Furthermore, **Toxel.com** is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information that **Toxel.com** collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances it is disclosed.
